Sure, it feels
like it's a
like it's
hype cycle because
capital spending
in the tech
and telecom sectors
telecom sectors
as a percent
of GDP is
a percent
nearly as high
nearly as
now as it
was during the
was during
tech and telecom
bubble.
But if you
will remember, the
will remember,
tech and telecom
bubble laid fiber,
bubble laid
and most of
it remained dark.
remained dark.
Today, the GPUs
Today, the
are driving
this cycle.
And I'll steal
from Brad Gerstner
Brad Gerstner
at Altimeter.
He's saying,
"Those aren't dark.
"Those aren't
They're in short
supply, and they
are being used."
being used."
And we agree
completely with that.
completely with
We compare this
capital spending cycle
capital spending
to the railroads
in the 1800s.
the 1800s.
That got up
to 5% to
to 5%
6% of GDP.
6% of
And then